<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context="com.vinaysomawat.nitwsyllabus.MainActivity">
    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content">
        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="380dp"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/idView"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="16dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:text="Course ID:CS382 \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tCredit:3\nPre-requisites:None\n"
                />
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/idView1"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#2002b6"
                android:textSize="16dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:text="Detailed syllabus:\n"
                />
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/firstpara"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:textColor="#7c051b"
                android:textSize="18dp"
                android:text="Features of Distributed versus Centralized Databases, Principles Of Distributed Databases, Levels Of Distribution Transparency, Reference Architecture for Distributed Databases, Types of Data Fragmentation, Integrity Constraints in Distributed Databases.\n\nTranslation of Global Queries to Fragment Queries, Equivalence Transformations for Queries, Transforming Global Queries into Fragment Queries, Distributed Grouping and Aggregate Functions, Evaluation of Parametric Queries.\n\nOptimization of Access Strategies, A Framework for Query Optimization, Join Queries, General Queries.\n\nThe Management of Distributed Transactions, A Framework for Transaction Management , Supporting Atomicity of Distributed Transactions, Concurrency Control for Distributed Transactions, Architectural Aspects of Distributed Transactions.\n\nConcurrency Control, Foundation of Distributed Concurrency Control, Distributed Deadlocks, Concurrency Control based on Timestamps, Optimistic Methods for Distributed Concurrency Control.\n\nReliability, Basic Concepts, Non-blocking Commitment Protocols, Reliability and concurrency Control, Determining a Consistent View of the Network, Detection and Resolution of Inconsistency, Checkpoints and Cold Restart, Distributed Database Administration, Catalogue Management in Distributed Databases, Authorization and Protection\n\nArchitectural Issues, Alternative Client/Server Architectures, Cache Consistency Object Management, Object Identifier Management, Pointer Swizzling, Object Migration, Distributed Object Storage, Object Query Processing, Object Query Processor Architectures, Query Processing Issues, Query Execution , Transaction Management, Transaction Management in Object DBMSs , Transactions as Objects. \n\nDatabase Integration, Scheme Translation, Scheme Integration, Query Processing Query Processing Layers in Distributed Multi-DBMSs, Query Optimization Issues. Transaction Management Transaction and Computation Model Multi-database Concurrency Control, Multi-database Recovery, Object Orientation And Interoperability Object Management Architecture CORBA and Database Interoperability Distributed Component Model COM/OLE and Database Interoperability, PUSH-Based Technologies.\n\nCurrent trends in No SQL and New SQL data management issues on the cloud, Stream data management"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/reading"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="18dp"
                android:text="\nReading:"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/readingpara"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:textColor="#047b31"
                android:textSize="18dp"
                android:text="1. M. Stonebraker, Readings in Database Systems, 2nd Edition, Morgan Kauffman, 1993.\n2. M T Ozsu, Patrick Valduriez, Principles of Distributed Database Systems, Prentice Hall, 1999\n3. S. Ceri and G. Pelaggati, Distributed Database System Principles and Systems, MGH, 1985.\n"/>
            <Button
                android:id="@+id/button"
                android:layout_width="340dp"
                android:layout_height="40dp"
                android:textSize="10dp"
                android:background="@color/colorPrimaryDark"
                style="@style/Widget.AppCompat.Button.Colored"
                android:layout_marginLeft="15dp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="15dp"
                android:text="Next Course"
                android:onClick="nextclickad"/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</RelativeLayout>