<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context="com.vinaysomawat.nitwsyllabus.MainActivity">
    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content">
        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="380dp"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/idView"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="16dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:text="Course ID:CS482 \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tCredit:3\nPre-requisites:None\n"
                />
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/idView1"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#2002b6"
                android:textSize="16dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:text="Detailed syllabus:\n"
                />
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/firstpara"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:textColor="#7c051b"
                android:textSize="18dp"
                android:text="INTRODUCTION – Agents and Objects – Evaluation of Agents – Agent Design Philosophies - Multi-agent System – Mobile Agents – Agent Communication – Knowledge query and Manipulation Language – Case Study.\n\nINTRODUCTION – What is AI? , The Foundations of Artificial Intelligence; - INTELLIGENT AGENTS – Agents and Environments, Good Behavior: The Concept of Rationality, The Nature of Environments, The Structure of Agents; - SOLVING PROBLEMS BY SEARCH – Problem-Solving Agents, Formulating problems, Searching for Solutions, Uninformed Search Strategies, Breadth-first search, Depth-first search, Searching with Partial Information, Informed (Heuristic) Search Strategies, Greedy best-first search, A* Search: Minimizing the total estimated solution cost, Heuristic Functions, Local Search Algorithms and Optimization Problems, Online Search Agents and Unknown Environments; –ADVERSARIAL SEARCH – Games, The minimax algorithm, Optimal decisions in multiplayer games, Alpha-Beta Pruning, Evaluation functions, Cutting off search, Games that Include an Element of Chance; - LOGICAL AGENTS – Knowledge-Based agents, The Wumpus World, Logic, Propositional Logic: A Very Simple Logic, Reasoning Patterns in Propositional Logic, Resolution, Forward and Backward chaining; - FIRST ORDER LOGIC – Syntax and Semantics of First-Order Logic, Using First-Order Logic , Knowledge Engineering in First-Order Logic; - INFERENCE IN FIRST ORDER LOGIC – Propositional vs. First-Order Inference, Unification and Lifting, Forward Chaining, Backward Chaining, Resolution ; - UNCERTAINTY – Acting under Uncertainty, Basic Probability Notation, The Axioms of Probability, Inference Using Full Joint Distributions, Independence, Bayes’ Rule and its Use, The Wumpus World Revisited; - PROBABILISTIC REASONING – Representing Knowledge in an Uncertain Domain, The Semantics of Bayesian Networks, Efficient Representation of Conditional Distribution, Exact Inference in Bayesian Networks, Approximate Inference in Bayesian Networks; -\n\nSTATISTICAL LEARNING METHODS – Statistical Learning, Learning with Complete Data, Learning with Hidden Variables: EM Algorithm."/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/reading"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="18dp"
                android:text="\nReading:"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/readingpara"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:textColor="#047b31"
                android:textSize="18dp"
                android:text="1. Stuart Russell, Peter Norvig, Artificial Intelligence -A Modern Approach, 2/e, Pearson, 2003.
2. Nils J Nilsson, Artificial Intelligence: A New Synthesis, Morgan Kaufmann Publications,2000.\n"/>
            <Button
                android:id="@+id/button"
                android:layout_width="340dp"
                android:layout_height="40dp"
                android:textSize="10dp"
                android:background="@color/colorPrimaryDark"
                style="@style/Widget.AppCompat.Button.Colored"
                android:layout_marginLeft="15dp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="15dp"
                android:text="Next Course"
                android:onClick="nextclickiag"/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</RelativeLayout>