<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context="com.vinaysomawat.nitwsyllabus.MainActivity">
    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content">
        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="380dp"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/idView"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="16dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:text="Course ID:CS451 \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tCredit:3\nPre-requisites:None\n"
                />
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/idView1"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#2002b6"
                android:textSize="16dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:text="Detailed syllabus:\n"
                />
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/firstpara"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:textColor="#7c051b"
                android:textSize="18dp"
                android:text="Basic communication Technologies, Introduction to Mobile Networks, Introduction to different categories of Wireless networks (MANET: Mobile ad-hoc networks- Communication Architectures of a typical MANET, Applications of MANET, WSN: Wireless Sensor Networks- topologies in WSN-Linear, Grid and Cluster based topologies, communication architectures in a WSN, applications of WSNs, VANET: Vehicular Ad-hoc Networks- communication architectures in VANET, Applications of VANET, PAN: Personal Area Networks- the Bluetooth technology, the blue tooth specifications, DTN: Delay Tolerant Network-delay tolerant network architecture, applications of DTN), Wireless Communication Fundamentals, Cellular Wireless Networks.\n\nMedium Access Control Layer- Hidden terminal problem, Exposed terminal problem, Collision avoidance, Congestion Avoidance, Congestion control, Energy Efficiency, MACA and MACAW protocols, Wireless LAN and IEEE 802.11- Network architecture, the physical layer, the MAC layer, security.\n\nDetailed network layer functionalities in multi-hop wireless networks- Mobile Ad-hoc Networks- broadcasting in a MANET, Flooding generated broadcast storm problem, rebroadcasting schemes, Issues in providing multicasting in MANET, Multicast routing protocols, Geocasting- Geocast routing protocols. Mobile Network Layer (Mobile IP), DHCP (Dynamic hostconfiguration protocol), Routing in Mobile Ad hoc Networks (MANET)- Topology-based versus position based approaches, Proactive routing protocols, Reactive routing protocols, Hybrid routing protocols, position based routing issues and forwarding strategies, AODV (Ad-hoc On-Demand Distance Vector Routing Protocol)- Analysis of AODV under mobility and Faults in a network, DSR (Dynamic Source Routing)-Analysis of DSR under mobility and Faults in a network, Secure routing protocols in MANET, Wireless Sensor Networks: (Routing protocols, Localization methods, Sensor Deployment Strategies), traffic flow pattern in WSN- one to many, many to one and many to many, Routing protocols for Delay Tolerant Networks, Routing protocols for Vehicular Ad-hoc Networks, Wireless Access Protocol, GPS (Global positioning system) and applications, RFID and its applications."/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/reading"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="18dp"
                android:text="\nReading:"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/readingpara"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:textColor="#047b31"
                android:textSize="18dp"
                android:text="1. C D M Cordeiro, D. P. Agarwal, Adhoc and Sensor Networks: Theory and applications, World Scientific, 2006.\n2. Jochen Schiller, Mobile Communications, Second Edition, Pearson Education, 2003.\n3. Asoke K Talukder and Roopa R. Yavagal, Mobile Computing – Technology, Applications and Service Creation; TMH Pub., New Delhi, 2006\n"/>
            <Button
                android:id="@+id/button"
                android:layout_width="340dp"
                android:layout_height="40dp"
                android:textSize="10dp"
                android:background="@color/colorPrimaryDark"
                style="@style/Widget.AppCompat.Button.Colored"
                android:layout_marginLeft="15dp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="15dp"
                android:text="Next Course"
                android:onClick="nextclickmls"/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</RelativeLayout>