<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context="com.vinaysomawat.nitwsyllabus.MainActivity">
    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content">
        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="380dp"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/idView"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="16dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:text="Course ID:CS351 \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tCredit:4\nPre-requisites:CS301:Theory of Computation\n"
                />
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/idView1"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#2002b6"
                android:textSize="16dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:text="Detailed syllabus:\n"
                />
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/firstpara"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:textColor="#7c051b"
                android:textSize="18dp"
                android:text="Phases of Compilers - Compiler Construction Tools - Bootstrapping\n\nLexical analyzer - The Role of the Lexical Analyzer, Input Buffering, Specification of Tokens, Recognition of Tokens, A Language for Specifying Lexical Analyzers.\n\nParsing - The Role of the Parser, Context-Free Grammars, Top-Down Parsing, Bottom-Up Parsing, Operator-Precedence Parsing, LR Parsers, Using Ambiguous Grammars, Parser Generators.\n\nSyntax-Directed Translation- Syntax-Directed Definitions, Construction of Syntax Trees, Bottom-Up Evaluation of S-Attributed Definitions, L-Attributed Definitions, Top Down Translation, Bottom-Up Evaluation of Inherited Attributes, Recursive Evaluators, Space for Attribute Values at Compile Time, Assigning Spaces at Compiler-Construction Time, Analysis of Syntax-Directed Definitions.\n\nType Checking- Type Systems, Specification of a Simple Type Checker, Equivalence of Type Expressions, Type Conversions, Overloading of Functions and Operators, Polymorphic Functions, An algorithm for Unification.\n\nRun-Time Environments - Source Language Issues, Storage Organization, Storage-Allocation Strategies, Access to Nonlocal Names, Parameter Passing, Symbol Tables, Language Facilities for Dynamic Storage Allocation, Dynamic Storage Allocation Techniques, Storage Allocation in Fortran.\n\nIntermediate Code Generation - Intermediate Languages, Declarations, Assignment Statements, Boolean Expressions, Case Statements, Backpatching, Procedure Calls.\n\nCode Generation - Issues in the Design of a Code Generator, The Target Machine, Run-Time Storage Management, Basic Blocks and Flow Graphs, Next-Use Information, A Simple Code Generator, Register Allocation and Assignment, The Dag Representation of Basic Blocks, Peephole Optimization, Generating Code from DAGs, Dynamic Programming Code-Generation Algorithm, Code-Generator Generators"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/reading"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="18dp"
                android:text="\nReading:"/>
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/readingpara"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:textColor="#047b31"
                android:textSize="18dp"
                android:text="1. Aho, Ravi Sethi, Monica S Lam, Ullman, Compilers - Principles, Techniques and Tools, 2nd Edition, Pearson, 2002.\n2. Randy Allen, Ken Kennedy, Optimizing Compilers for Modern Architectures, Morgan Kauffmann, 2001.\n"/>
            <Button
                android:id="@+id/button"
                android:layout_width="340dp"
                android:layout_height="40dp"
                android:textSize="10dp"
                android:background="@color/colorPrimaryDark"
                style="@style/Widget.AppCompat.Button.Colored"
                android:layout_marginLeft="15dp"
                android:layout_marginBottom="15dp"
                android:text="Next Course"
                android:onClick="nextclicklp"/>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</RelativeLayout>